From the shadows of the subconscious to the chaos of the cosmic scrolls, this is Psyche Awakens.
Crowd, whoosh, sparkly chimes, thundercrack.
You smooth mystical.
Yo, welcome to the madness, buckle in tight, tear it on deck, third eye in flight.
Trolls be dropping, spirits in the chat and the vibes ain't stopping
Lenore's on guard, tricks bringin' love
Lola, Rudy Marble's fan from above
It's like the Awake has stepped in the flame
We call your truth, we say your name
It's wild, it's real, it's so deep play
Now grab your tea and slay the dead
It's like the Awake has, don't look away
Your shadow's talking, it came to stay
We laugh, we cry, we speak
We scream live from the madness, this ain't no dream
What's up? Okay. Um, you know ghost is kind of the kind of mad. Hey, what's up?
Yes, it goes come to go shows it goes shows up. He can decide who comes on and
off the panel for this until
Hey summer, I don't know if he'll show up though. I'll give him some control the
panel just for just for tonight. Like he I think like, you know, you should save the
You know taking off people that he really wants off. So Florida diamond easier kicked off until you know tomorrow night
He brought some our back. I'll give him back his boot that he used on her. So he's got two left. I think so
You know, that's the best way I can keep it there. I hope he's a hey, what's up, young compost?
But if he doesn't show up right now, then I guess he's somewhere else and we'll have to do it another time for his running the panel
Okay
Ghosty I'll wait for him for like five minutes. Oh wait actually until 7 p.m.. If he doesn't show up until 7 p.m..
I'll just open up the panel
Yeah, so let's read day three of this book this book will change your life
So this is day three it says
Day three
Um, it says throw today throw away something that you'd like. Oh, that's a hard one
Here's a picture. That's all it says right there
Has all these pictures, you know, you like I don't want to do that. If I like it, I don't want to throw it away
Anyway, I guess those are some ideas. Let's go to day four. It says day four. I need my glasses. Let me see
And if you didn't show up you want to
Cash my panel in okay
Absolutely at 7 p.m. I'll open up the panel for summer for summer's live
Okay, it says world coloring day is pretty for today. Work out your globetrotting plans for the rest of your time on earth
And get on the phone to the accredited travel agent the State Department currently
Discourage its travel to the following countries Afghanistan Iraq North Korea Turkey
Manistans and Bobway North Yemen fill in country by country been there done that intend to go there this year
Intend to go there some time before I die or happy to never set foot in there my whole life
That's a little word world map
Kind of cool
Yeah
No problem. No problem
Yeah, I do want to make it bear and so it's like even if you know you donate like you know
I will I'll save if you don't cat, you know use your you know the
The panel of the cake that night, you know, I'll carry them over so I'm keeping better track of it
But I don't know if he'll be back right now. I didn't have to I had to walk to the store to get cigars real quick and
Came back as I ran as fast as I could but I just needed some more cigars. Okay, so we're all good
Yeah, so, you know, I was thinking I'm trying to make a website and it's kind of hard to do the website without the computer
So when I get the computer, I'll be able to make a website for the
for the show, you know, it was just the company, right and
Still trying to figure out the tick-tock thing why I can't stream from there right now
Might have been because I was smoking on the panel
Or on the channel
It's like what happened to my e-bike my e-bike is fine
My neighbors actually they were moving and they asked if they could use my garage and I said yes
And so then I like she's like, okay. Well, we're gonna buy you the part you need for your bike
But then they moved they moved like 10 10 minutes away
So they she said he's gonna come over soon as they have some time and he'll come over and have a look
they got they got the part and
I guess they're just busy moving in so
It's fine. It's just sitting in the garage waiting for it waiting to be fixed if it doesn't they don't fix that
I'll just take it to a shop. It's just the charger the charging port is fried right now
Yeah, they were super cool really nice the good neighbors
I'm disappointed they left. There's a nice little there's a nice couple like a nice Asian couple that moved in and cats are
Already saying hi there. Hey Gotti. Hey, I'm yonny summer. I had a members and everybody else evil Ronald McDonald LES yon
Hi everybody, yeah, I'll be on for I'll try to do a few hours a few hours more at least
Till 10 p.m. So summer is going to take control the panel in a few minutes. It goes doesn't show up to you
Next time goes showed this show up. I'll let him
You know that there's no panel running I'll let him
He wants to decide who comes on and off the panel for a few hours. I'll be fine with that
I'll let him I'll let him go. I'll let him control that that part of it. I'll say you have to use your timeouts for later
You know, I hope it's fair. I try to make it. Hey, Jay dog. How are you guys?
so
Yeah, so it's good to see you guys it is now
Sunday, so I'm gonna pull out these cards and do a collective with the alien deck
There's some dogs working outside
There's the alien deck. Okay. Hey, J-Dog. Okay.
Turned over. Oh shit, okay, she turned over. He's popped out. Oh, magician. Okay, page of wands.
Third card. Six of wands. Okay. Okay, so...
You're waiting for it. You've been manifesting something even working on manifesting something and so one's gonna come and
Bring it to you, but you're just waiting for them still looks like you're still waiting. Okay. Let's get a couple more
It's our okay
Something maybe unexpected might happen. Okay. Now we have this upside down the moon upside down, but this will be made clear
Moon right side up is like, you know illusion, but moon upside down is like it will be clear
Something will be made clear about this and we had ace of wands, but you'll have the power to overcome any of this
I've seen page last night. Yeah, and so there's the ace of wands
It's like, you know, that's it's a big there's something that will make you really passionate will come and
Out of any kind of negativity that happens or out of the sudden change, right?
This will all be made clear to you also my words of advice for the chat three of swords. Okay
It's like to get over heartbreak. It looks like to
Or not to have your heart broken because
They're gonna think of the great advice of the three of swords. It's like
Usually the heartbreak card, but I think it's like kind of warning about
Heartbreak and maybe that's your head guide and not your heart in the situation. So a few more
Eight of cups. Okay. There's a lot of good options out there. You got your cups are full. Okay?
You might want to still be going for those other two cups
Temperance upside down try to be more
Try to stay more balanced right now
watch watch your
Your intake of
You know
Intoxicants and we have the world and so the world means that you will come through the cycle
Successively and into the news cycle. Okay
That's for everybody in the chat.
If you'd like a reading on the show tonight,
just let me know.
Members can just put the crystal ball in the chat.
And I will read you or just,
if you don't, not a member,
just type your question or type general.
I'll get you two.
Members, you get priority more cards,
but I'll be happy to get anybody and everybody.
Okay, so I'm just shuffling.
So let's wait until,
and tell me how many cards you would like if you...
Hey, Jamie that page is very sweet. Hey, just sweet, but she has a salty side, you know, another one gets to see it
Little bit salty too sweet and salty like a yes
So yeah, and we want to check out prairie pay prairie winds and wildflowers spiritual arts, that's her channel. She does lives now
Okay
I hope everyone's doing good.
There's a few more minutes, so we'll see.
If Ghost comes back, if not, Ghost
will have to cash in his panel later.
And Summer, I think, would like the panel at 7 to 10.
So I'm going to start creating the banner for that.
And Summer, thank you, Summer.
Summer and talk your ish.
These are summer channel names hot mess summer and
Talk your ish
Okay, until 10 p.m
Starting in a couple minutes, but I have that ready
Hopefully he'll show back up
Yep, you got four minutes now three minutes. You got three minutes to go goes gonna show up. We'll see
Hopefully, you know, hopefully he's not mad. I do want to make sure I'm totally fair. Yeah, I got the link for you
Here you go
Okay, it doesn't look like he's gonna come so I
Think we did wait
Wait long enough don't put the banner up for summer
So open panel till 10 p.m. Pacific Standard Time and
Thank you so much summer for sponsoring the panel
Yep, I don't see ghosts anywhere
So this works out perfect because you know and she does get to use her panel and
Then she shouldn't be kicked off of the day that's her panel is so
Now just kind of protect her until tomorrow
So but I am very thankful to ghosts. I've been looking at some new computers and stuff and
What happened?
Not too much. It was like, you know ghosts like ghosts kind of
Take control of the panel, but he can't make up his mind. Oh shit
Looking at I sent I sent tiktok a message
And it says, hi there, thanks for reaching out.
We should be looking at your account
and it has no current violations,
so it should be accessible to you.
If you're going to, if you're still unable to access
your account, please respond directly to us
here with the following information.
Once you get the information, we'll review
and help you get it resolved, okay?
That was pretty fast that they got back to me.
Okay, and I'll just change the title
to summer takes control, summer's open panel, okay.
Okay
So we'll get it all
See, I'm just son
Okay
Here we go
Hi
Yeah, so thank you for sponsoring the panel. He never came. Oh
He never came. Okay. I was gonna say I'll give him another 10 minutes to get here
Okay, well, I didn't put the banner I have your banner and everything
But you know, I don't think I think he went somewhere else maybe but I'll give him his open panels another time
You know, I'm gonna make sure I make it fair and get he gets his money worth
But you know, I think that you know, I don't I just wanted I was trying to help a little bit. I think he wants to
You know, he likes summer and I don't think that I don't know I don't think that they should have conflicts and so
Hopefully this that will help out. But yeah, okay. Well, how are you? So anybody's welcome up? We have open panel tonight
And here's I can't make up his mind on summer
so I
Just kind of helped him out a little bit
Yeah, you gotta go home. You gotta get out of here.
So there's a link.
It looks okay. I'll get a pin and everything for everybody.
Okay.
Okay. I'll get the link pin.
There's a new spot on it. You're gonna be a brand new man, but it's all done.
Sorry, it's Friday. I get my new lay.
I thought I was getting it last Friday, but they did it was just a walk around and get a feel for it. No, okay
Well, good luck, sweetie. Thanks man. You're doing
There's the uh, I was grabbing some pop real quick. Uh, no problem. There's
Got the link pin for everybody whose band is easy and easy easy and diamond are banned for 24 hours
And then, that's not the chatterbait link, that is the stream yard link for people on the panel on BSBB.
Hey, Ghost! I won, motherfucker!
No, I'm just kidding. Not really, though.
Well, you're gonna make up in that guy auto was I mean he was pretty interesting. I don't know. He's like uh, he seemed like
I know
Yeah, and thank you a Jade date see for uh recommending my show to him and thank you everybody that recommends the show and
Bring some new new people in here. It's the I think we're have a fun time meeting some people so
so are easy so since goes banned them on his panel would they be banned on his his panel
well no i think no i think that he did the 24 hour but i don't think it was like he
he would have the panel banned so i'll just i'll all respect his uh his uh those two bands but
but he kept bringing you right back twice i was like okay well he you know can't make up his mind
I'd rather have him use it on somebody he really wants to be.
He takes off.
Anybody else?
Yeah.
Sorry, Jamie.
I can't transfer the bands, but nice try, Jamie, though.
This is sweet of you.
Hey, Canada Dry, how are you doing?
You're welcome on the panel.
We're here with Summer.
She's fallen through the panel for the next few hours, the open panel.
Yeah
And take a shower and all that okay, okay, okay sounds good
I'm not gonna I'm not gonna spend five billion dollars to take his voice away from him
Okay
Well, it's you tell him he's allowed to come sit on my panel if he would like
Okay, I think that'll be good news for him, so
Actually, will you pull some cards for me first?
Sure, absolutely. Got my alien deck right here. Let's see.
Let's give it some shuffles.
Do you have a question or just a general?
Just a general.
I like these cards, they're like easier to shuffle for me
because they're like kind of small.
Okay, so let's see.
Oh, we have the Queen of Cups.
And so like really in control of, you know,
and in your emotions and very, you know,
Queen of Cups is just an abundant flowing,
flowing goodness and love.
We also have a Wheel of Fortune.
It looks like things are in your favor right now.
It's a lucky time right now.
This is like in the present position.
It's a good time. So maybe I don't know if you buy lottery tickets or something, but or just in general you've got good luck
We also have the ten of wands. You also do carry a lot of you carry a lot of other people's stuff sometimes, you know
Sometimes some of their burdens and so remember you can sometimes put those down
I'd have to carry everything, you know, okay, so we have this nine of swords also
So this is like have you been getting enough rest or like?
Because it kind of indicates that you might be having it's like some kind of like worries keep you up sometimes
Yeah, I've had some I got some pretty heavy court cases going on right now not for me, but as an advocate
Okay
So I see the three of wands and see they're going like 33 right there or like 33
But this three of wands, it's like working together with some other people that are also passionate and
Working with a common a common goal like so also power of three I would say
Which is a you know been magic a very powerful number
Okay, and also five of cups and so this is like kind of like you this is a five of cups in the upright is regressed
And so this upside down I mean you don't have regrets
and you basically, you do what you feel is right
and you stand behind it, okay?
Let me see a couple more.
There's some stuff still to be revealed.
This is the moon.
It'll be revealed in time.
It doesn't wanna come out in the deck necessarily
and some advice.
Yeah, you got the advice of temperance
and that's just to stay balanced
and take one hand with the other hand.
Don't go to too many extremes.
Okay, you have the the Hierophant and so this is like saying like this higher power is guiding you
And this almost reminds me of Kali a little bit because of the arms it looks in the blue skin
But you know it's an alien, but it does remind me of like this this higher power helping you along
and
Watching over you guiding. So I hope you like that
That was your re-en
You're welcome
Pleasure any time
It's kind of scary looking yeah, they're a little bit they're a little bit of a you know these aliens aren't the friendliest looking aliens, but
You know the grazer kind of said to be kind of emotionless, but I think it's an interesting deck pretty cool deck, so
Okay
Love you
Yeah, anyone else would like a reading from these cards or I got a also I got the rainbow tarot
I got the cat tarot. I got the Van Gogh tarot and
the
Monster tarot, so if anyone wants the card and you can pick your deck just let me know
And of course does show up I'll let him do his panel at 10 p.m
If he's here. Okay, so Jamie would like another one. I'll use a few cards Jamie
eight of pentacles
You got some kind of strength and material material right now, hold on me the cards I
Think okay. I'm using the alien one again
This eight of pentacles is also like you know being able to balance like a lot of a lot of things in different hands
like having a lot of kind like the octopus alien right there having to having a
It's a lot of useful things in your hands.
Okay, we got the moon.
Again, this is like things are not all meant
to be revealed right now,
but there's some things that are hidden still.
They will be revealed as the moon cycle continues
and we've got the page of pentacles, but it's in reverse.
Okay, this could mean that you'll be bringing
somebody else something instead of them bringing it to you.
Okay, let's see and we have the night of wants and so yeah, also, I just get this feeling like you're gonna be going to keep somebody
like
Instead of them coming to you you're gonna have to go to them
Devon of swords, but
Also, if you've been worried about somebody stealing anything you don't have to worry about it things like all your property is safe
There's no there's no deception or thievery seen around you. Okay?
The magician, you have this ability to manifest everything you want in your life.
You take in the power from above for being able to take it to the power below, okay?
As above, so below, okay?
Some advice for Jamie, I'll give a couple cards of advice.
Okay, you got the Empress.
Come into your Queenly powers.
Here's the Empress card too.
There you go.
You know all queens and stick really come into your your full power with all the elements to clean in that the emperors and the magician kind of together
It's like just
Manifesting yourself into that and this is the truth. Okay. You got the ace of swords
This is the truth and speak also speak your truth. So continue and yes, you do speak your truth and
You are able to manifest and so I hope you like that Jamie
Anyone else when a reading from any deck you're welcome. You're very welcome
If not, you know, the panel's open, open panel.
Feel free to join.
Let's see this, oh my,
charger's not working 100%.
Let's see.
Okay.
Yeah, so that's good news from the,
good news from TikTok that it says my,
I should have full,
Streaming rights. I just have no idea why it's not working right now. It's not working any of my phones and it says
It says no live access for some reason, so I'm not quite sure kind of getting concerned a little bit
Because they don't even know what's going on with it. So
Let's see what I got for us, you know anybody here I
Can uh
See I could find a
Let's go through this book until we also open to a random page
The random page says start an urban myth
See how fast the rumor can spread to be successful in urban myth must include two or more of the following elements
Imaginative revenge by a jilted lover pets life ending in a gruesome circumstance preferably sexual hit in deadly flaw in consumer products
For example, a man in Chicago decides to take revenge on his wife, ex-wife, by poisoning
her CAT by mixing a huge dose of powerful painkillers xyleanol in the cat food.
I don't like this story.
Xyleanol, however, has large quantities in aproposgiac to cats.
So the cat didn't die, but instead RAPED, the ex-husband's favorite gerbil to death.
Oh, no.
What to do if you live in a non-urban area? Don't worry. The historical answer to the urban myth is the fisherman's tale
Ancestor is a fisherman's tale be aware that it spreads less rapidly however and that subject matter is slightly more restrictive
Tails was to be based mainly around catching a very big fish
There you go
Urban myth
Hey Bulbasack, how are you? Okay, so we have Trevor here. Hello
How we doing friend, can you hear me okay? I do I can't how are you today beautiful beautiful?
I I heard you say if anybody wants to come up on the panel, and I I thought I'd take my
Opportunity here to catch up with my old pal psych house. Yeah
Fine. Oh, I'm doing pretty good, you know, and then some are also sponsored this panel tonight
You know we had ghosts here earlier ghosts did donate a lot this week
And I'll be able to buy a computer now and your computer and it'll help really help the show
Yeah
I've been eating I've been eating the one that I was like I'll never be able to afford one or anything and then
but uh
Thanks to some very generous donations. I will be able to and it'll really really really help the show. Thank you
Do you have an idea what what what brand if you will well, they have these mini PCs now
They're like small and they're like a few hundred bucks
And I just need something that I can plug my you know
USB microphone into and I can plug my my VR headset into if I can do that and I have windows
And I can play some video games. I'll be very happy. So it should be a couple hundred, two hundred, three hundred bucks.
Very nice, very nice. That's awesome. Do you remember the first computer you ever had in the nineties or whatever kind of computer?
Well, it was maybe like I don't know if it was a compact, but it was maybe the computer's not even around
It was a it was called a 486 and that was like the one step above the 386
So it's called the 486 and I had Carmen San Diego on it. I had like a screensaver
I had maybe a few just like little dot matrix games
And then the next computer I had with the gateway after that and I got the gateway and that had actually like the internet on it
Actually did the first computer I have have the internet. I think it might have had
Oh, they used to have these BBS remember the BBS's they had there before the internet. There's bulls and boards
predates me
predate me
Yeah, they have these bulletin boards and you would got it was kind of like looked like the it was in the green
You know they have a green typing on the computers and stuff like that the computer screen used to be just green and black
That's what they used to look like and so
Yeah, it was a long time ago. It was probably 1993 or 1994, you know, and so
That's before we got a computer for sure that's before we got one hey
Can I tell you about the first computer we got if you don't mind of course don't mind
God, it must have been early to like 2001 probably
There was a poverty a poverty brand of computers and they called them e-machines
They called them e-machines
Yeah, that that was the
Yeah, that was the you know the big tower the big friend white
grayish monitor or whatever and yeah and we were putting the AOL disc in them to get free internet
You know just connect the phone line to the back of the tower so we can get out for our AOL
Yeah, they would have the AOL these like heartless floppy disks and then they got CDs later
But you put in a floppy disk set up for AOL and AOL was like the shit
That was like the numbs. I was like the only way to get on the internet basically. I think they might have had it like another
Buddy you're showing your age. I don't remember floppy disks. Was that a thing for AOL?
Well, yeah, they had
Yeah, they had floppy this before they had not that's a big one
They did these big floppy this right?
He's like they were actually floppy and then they had these hard disk that were smaller
And those were like the next generation floppy then they came out with the CDs
But the floppy is only held a few a few megabytes of RAM and stuff. I
Honestly, why you're predating me you're predating me. I always
because they don't know a goddamn thing,
but here you are just schooling me.
Yeah, I always remember just the CDs, the discs.
I didn't know they had the floppies.
Oh, wow.
I think so.
Well, I am 44, so, you know,
I think I'm the 10 years older than you about, so.
Maybe it almost or almost a decade
Okay, I'll go ten years
Seven years
77 years that's still like the difference between when I would but I would have been a senior in high school
You would have been a sixth grade, right? So quite a quite, you know, I'm quite a bit over the edge away
You don't say in what year I graduated 99
Okay, I was
Oh, yeah, so eight years
Can you believe that like I think about it like like I said, I like I just said I was I graduating in 2007
It's gonna be 30
Not 30 years 20 years
Since I graduated in a in a couple of years and it's like what the fuck happened
Like January members though
January members when they had the floppies, right?
Yeah, had you guys you ever play Carmen San Diego? That was like there's like a few games like
Yes, fuck yeah
But yeah, well it wasn't if I correctly it was a cartoon, but later they also did a game show, right?
They did a game show
But it really started out as a computer as a computer game at first and then they based the TV show on the computer game
And you'd always try to find Carmen San Diego around the world
And you would have little clues about what country she's in or you don't you'd always miss her and stuff
and a pretty cool game.
You remember the early M.S. paint?
Yeah, the M.S. paint, you could make a little drawing
and then print it out on a,
the printer paper used to be in a little,
had perforated kind of like little cutout circles
along the side.
It would just be fed through this inkjet
or it was an inkjet or some kind of,
So really was really had like five colors and stuff like that. You know, it's pretty crazy
It's like can you help me out on this one? I'm trying to remember this. I remember this as a kid
It was a Nickelodeon game show. It was like American Gladiators, but for kids. Oh, yeah
Well, it's a double dare. You can't it was maybe like kids. I was called. What's it kids got?
Who was this show is called like?
No, it was like a big rock statue type, Aztec.
Oh, the Aztec, yeah.
Who knows that show, Temple of Doom.
So there you go, the Temple of Doom.
That's what it was called.
It was called the Temple.
I think it was called the Temple.
Yeah, look it up.
Where's Waldo and it was like American gladiators for kids
Yeah, they did it was the but it was like yeah, like a Mayan temple kind of themed or Aztec temple
right
Nickelodeon game show 80s or the 80s or 90s might have been the 90s. I think it was 90s
Yeah, it ends of the hidden temple. Yeah, the temple something. Yeah, something about legends of the hidden temple
I really didn't watch it. I watched like are you I watched nick they said snick and that was or nick and night
Right or nick and night was like they played like I love Lucy and the Lucy show
But snick was like Saturday night Nickelodeon. They had are you free to the dark and they had
Other there's a so-called wild and crazy kids. I don't know if you remember that but they had like
They all got a t-shirt because they're wildly crazy kids
And some people would wear that kids incorporated. I remember that one. Okay. I DS kids incorporated
Do you remember zoobly zoo?
What is that? There's a really
Zoo there's a really creepy show called zoobly zoo and it was about this like he's like human
There are like adults, but they were dressed as like there's like a woman dressed like a parrot
You know a big beak and there was like benverine played like
Some kind of cat or something like that and they would run in simpy. Yep. I love running simpy
What else was on SNCC? Remember that, SNCC?
Can I say three words? Can I say three words for you?
See if this works tonight. Think about early 90s Nickelodeon.
Salute your shorts.
Oh, classic.
Yeah, what was the name of the counselor?
Either the counselor or the guy from the different strokes with the red hair.
Do you remember the guy from...
But you remember there's a redhead redheaded kid on that
He was actually like he played Sam on different strokes, but he'd like camp on I want to to hold our hearts
You're just thinking that Jamie. Yeah, I haven't thought about these. Oh, how about this? Hey, dude everyone remember hey, dude
It sounds familiar. It sounds familiar. I can't explain it, but it does sound
Well, it was kind of like this sort this dorky like Jewish guy like by the dude Rams to run and so then they had like melody
I was on and she played she was played by the the Marsha Brady Christine
Christina something yet
Yes, yes, sir. Yes, sir. Wow man, it's crazy. It's crazy how long it's been since
one of my one of my first earliest memories is my sister watching
It's so funny. It was ghost writers. It was
Ghost writer. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, the kids would be on this early 90s
Computer just a huge ass bucket monitor and all of a sudden the ghost writer
would start writing things on the computer, you know, no rhyme or reason and
Yeah, I remember my sister was into that and I think that's one of my first memories is that stupid ghost writer show
In fact, I found it years later. I found that episode. I remember and
I remember I was scared when I was a little kid because it was something to do with
They were wearing like it was
Teenagers wearing alien masks and just just ruckus. They were they were causing a ruckus
Yeah, there is a little kid, but I watched it years later, and I said my god. This is the stupidest shit. I've ever seen
Yeah, I mean about these like urban kids and then they would like solve mysteries and they would get like that
Yeah, so are typing on the screen like the answer to the mysteries. Exactly. Yeah
Lamp shop. Oh, it's lamb chops play along
Sing that and play along. I like that show even when I was like 12 or 13
I would like in middle school. I would be watching that so excited. I like love the
Sherry Lewis and lamb chop and I
You don't I'll show you a picture of a sherry Lewis sherry Lewis is like this sherry Lewis and lamb shop
Lamb shop was a little is that emperors chain?
Yes, I think she was on the the first time I ever came on your panel
awesome
Thinking who that is I could be yeah. No, you're right. You're right. You're right
And so here's the here's what she here's what she looked like, but she's she's a puppeteer for many years
That's a lamb shop
Oh, maybe I do remember that like
Hi, yeah, we hi, yeah, we it's you like a whole damn shopping. Yeah, it's pretty funny
A young cherry Lewis cherry Lewis looks pretty well, there's her daughter, but I think she was younger
She was yeah, here's when she was younger. She was quite a quite a dish
Oh, there we go. Yeah. Nice. Nice. Oh, I like having to remember. So, yeah, Janet's saying hello to you. Yes
I used to watch emptiness and the golden girls, you know, that was on Friday nights
I think and I used to call my grandma or maybe Saturday night
I call my grandma on the phone we watch the golden girls together on the phone and
When they got too sexual she was like hang up or
Talk real laughing. You're getting me distracted, but yeah, I was like probably like seven years old eight years old
Just call my grandma every weekend and watch it. Oh
Really the Golden Girls was that you and your nice? Very nice. That was our show. That was our show
Name the rest of the other room Atlanta hand and then it's still getty
with Sophia, Ruma Panahan was Blanche, Betty White was Rose, and
Bea Arthur was Dorothy. Hey, I'm Three's company. Yeah, that was like, I
loved Suzanne Summers, but she was only on the first season, I think, and then I would watch reruns of it.
I think he was like... Oh, Ritter, right? John Ritter, was that his name? I'm Three's company. Yep.
John Ritter, he played Jack, Jack Tripper, and it was a funny show because it was like all about
He was a straight guy, but then he had to say he was gay
So the landlord would let him move in with like, you know some women and stuff
And so we'd always like we do these gaugles. He'd be like, huh?
You know what they put with mr. Furley and something you'd be like, oh that guy's a little bit like this
There's a bit of a little imprisque. Yeah, Roseanne
And it's kind of funny like how ahead of its time that was though to have like at least someone pretending to be gay on the show or
Decided breast homosexuality, you know, maybe like it was a little bit little bit negative toward it
Maybe a little bit like oh my gosh like
Hey, I think I talked to you about this before
But I find this is consistent for every kid who grew up during the 90s
four letters, four letters, T G I F. Oh yeah. Those shows they showed up on Friday.
Step by step, full house, family matters, no one else was there. There was like four
shows back then. Mr. Cooper, sister, sister. I think you said family matters
already. Yeah. They switched them in and out pretty regularly.
Yeah, I like tears tears good. I like there's a show called small wonder I watched small wonder
I want you to build here. I'm that with tears. You're talking the 80s
You're talking you ever see you ever see mr. Belvedere mr. Belvedere ever seen that one
The only reason I know about that show is because I Marilyn Manson
the Marilyn Manson thing supposedly he wasn't that wasn't actually him right no
it wasn't the guy's name is Rob Stone and then they also said it was Paul from
the Wonder Years was also Marilyn Manson and he had his ribs removed and all
this stuff but no neither of them was actually Manson's father it was an
executive at Sony and that's how he got the Ricker contract
Pretty crazy, huh? A lot of people don't know that yeah, his father worked for Sony and so his father was a big manager for him. And so
But he was very good at a peevee's playhouse. Yeah, it was Saturday mornings and then yeah
Movies cocktail. Okay. How about what was that whoopie Goldberg and whoopie Goldberg used to be married to to a
Head dancing, right? And so I don't I think they did a movie together, but yeah, they got in trouble because
Yeah, they were married
The movie was called Ghost, but I didn't know they were married.
Oh, no, no, not Patrick Swayze.
It was Whoopi Goldberg and Ted Danson.
But and Ted, they went to a Friars Club roast and they went in black space.
And so that was like really or, you know, she didn't but he did.
You know, and so that was really controversial to appear.
Like, and so I thought that was kind of an.
for that. Didn't she get the
last name Goldberg through a
marriage because Goldberg is a
Jewish last name. I think I
think I think she I think she
just took it. She's like, I
think you know, I think she just
took that last name. I know her
first name is made up because
she had the flatulence issue,
so it's called whoopie like a
whoopie cushion. Oh mannequin.
Yeah, I remember that one.
But I don't know if she just made up Goldberg. I can look it up. Like how did how did she get the last name?
Maybe she was married to a Jewish man. Let me see how did whoopee, huh? What's that weird frickin?
Dearest or something like that. It's uh, it was produced by Oprah Winfrey
Whoopee Goldberg was in it and it was like this bizarre movie like back in the back in the 1800s
Back in the slave times and there was this little girl who was this but she was like possessed
It was like the most bizarre movie
Dearest, let me look that up mommy deer. Not mommy dearest
No, no, that was about John Collins. Hey, we have Roger Klotz on let me see. Hold on. I just one second
Let me just bring up this guest. Whoopee Goldberg filmography
Roger. What's up? Hey, what's up, dude?
I'm just showing hey, I noticed that you guys were talking about Marilyn Manson in the wonder years
Yeah, I figured I come up. Did you know that he had a rib removed so he could suck his own dick?
I don't believe that
Well, why do you think that?
Because his name is Brian Warner. He's like, you know, he's probably like ten years older than me
But he yeah, he was not the guy in Wonder Years was named Rob Stone
It was well known as the urban legend. He's also said it was so the guy from the Wonder Years
He went by Roscoe before he was named Marilyn Manson who's named Roscoe Manson
Rob Stone I said Rob Stone
Manson and it was in
It was not
It says it's the sweet first of, but the family member.
You can go on IMDB and look it up, though, dude.
It's true.
It's all true.
I read it on Wikipedia.
It says, it says, how's Lemay and Sen, also known
as Marilyn May and Sen.
And then it says, in parentheses, that he got a rib removed
in the mid-90s so he could suck his own hair.
It says he didn't have a surgery
But it was it was a fix his ear lobes and then he second fact
He was dating Rose McGowan at the time. He had no need to do it himself. Anyway, he was on an 86 come starts
This manson does act he filmed in view as in David Lynch's lost highway in 1997
He recently had sons of anarchy and some of our key, but there's he didn't he wasn't on it says
Do you know heavy makeup many do not know what he looks like for real so of course rumors are that he's
Yeah, that's why people get misinterpreted that he wasn't on the wonder years is because he's wearing all that makeup
And then he got a riddler so he could suck his own dick
Okay, well, that's interesting. Well, you know, who would do that though? I mean anybody really do that when Manson I
Don't believe it. Roger. What was his name?
Robstone, Robstone, Mr. Marilyn Manson
Brian Warner, Brian Warner
And it's like a Warner like Warner Brothers, right? And I think he worked for Sony
Did you know Malcolm Jamal Warner just died and he was one of the Warner Brothers because he was
Hey, I'm sorry. No, you're fine. Jamie
color purple
Well, that is what it was
He was black. He was a brown fellow. Oh
Please stop you're displaying with this Roger, but you're funny. I mean, what are you talking about?
I like your picture though. Let me look at your picture real quick.
What are you on? Hey, what's up?
I'm just one of these guys that Marilyn Manson suck his own wiener.
Well, I'm a very big Marilyn Manson fan. I was especially in the 90s.
I was probably a mechanical animal or a comb of white.
Yeah, full shit.
Como what was that none? I have something you don't know. You don't know what you're talking about because you think he's on the wonder years
You don't okay. Anyway, I don't know IMDb
It's does not yes, it does
It's hype and Robert stone aka mr. Manson aka the mechanical animal may have a Manson I
Don't believe it. Well, you believe it
What about any Christ superstars and that's the big
Yes, yes, yeah, he says that's his favorite album because that's the one that's the most well-known
How many times have you seen man to them person?
How many no, how many times have you seen man to them person? I've actually met him in person too. Oh, really?
No, 18 18 times
Okay, so I have more times than you man
Probably probably I've seen him about six or seven times, plus I met him though
But yeah, he's super fan art. He did an art show and I met him at the art show. Yeah, madam
Oh, yeah, did you buy any of his paintings? No, I bought I bought a poster and he signed it. I don't have it anymore though
Yeah, I did. Oh, yeah, you got rid of it. Yeah, you're a big man. I get rid of it
I move when I moved I lost it. I moved it. I lost it to a fan. Okay. Well, I'm not a fucking fan cut
I'm not anymore. Okay. Well, anyway, nice talking to you. Bye
Did I cause Empress Janet to leave because I brought up that movie?
I was trying to think of the color purple.
I don't think so.
Well, that's my cue to leave.
Well, I did explain it as a movie.
I think she was annoyed by the collar, the collar annoyed her or something.
I don't think it was you.
I hope she comes back or maybe somebody said something in the chat like about her.
I don't know.
She's been a little bit. I don't know but uh, hopefully everything's okay. How's everyone doing? I'm looking for some weed right now deliveries
Hey, you can't worry about everything, right? He can't yeah
Yeah
So what what was that? What was he trying to say about Marilyn Manson? I didn't even get all that
I was so focused on trying to figure out what that movie was
He was trying to say that he was he actually did try to suck his own dick and that he's
18 times and that he that I don't know shit about Marilyn Manson. Well, it's okay
I don't care. I don't really care. I'm not a Manson fan that much anymore, but I was a huge massive band in the 90s
Anyway, the only album I can name by Mary
Marilyn Manson is that anti-christ superstar and that's obviously because it's his biggest one
But I do remember a video and I think I might have brought this up to you
Marilyn Manson's on stage. I'm not sure if he's drunk or high off his ass, but he is just like
He's picking on Twiggy and just like beat the shit out of him.
Well, Twiggy's trying to play the guitar.
Marilyn Manson is just like, he's like bumping into him and slapping him.
And that's, that's the same right, Twiggy, the guitar player.
Yeah, Twiggy Ramirez, yeah, I think it was Twiggy Ramirez.
Um, yes, exactly and uh, I mean, it's awful, but it's hilarious
Yeah, I mean that was like the videos that he does backstage and he like beats up people and his own band and he was like
One time he's getting his dick sucked by some guy and like, you know in this like, I don't know
He was like they have trans sex genders back there. It's pretty wild for its time, right? But uh
You see I'm looking for like a good cartridge to buy. Oh, I don't know. That's the cartridge. I need to fall in one
What is that a cartridge is that we said as a herb is that with weed you know has has weed in it
I can get two of I can get two of these for like $30 to 60 plus 25% off is like 50
I think that will work that I'm back. Oh, it's just a battery though. That sucks
The weed and the vapes and whatnot
Yeah, I found it. Okay. I'd like to I'd like the vapes. Yeah, so uh, I
What are the ones that are all in one though? They don't have to put them on a battery. There are there's all in one
I've always just been a
I've never had a vape in my life
I've always just been a full-out alcoholic with poverty beers. The only time I've ever
really smoked weed is
When I'm hanging out with my dad and he has it around
my dad only smokes weed but other than that I've just uh I've never had a vape I've never had a
vape in all my years they seem to be popular they seem to be popular they are they are um and uh
I uh you know I I'd like them I think they're better than the uh
Some of us I'm just thinking oh here this one. Oh, this is 60 bucks. Ah, some of them are expensive
I don't I like to spend more than $50 on a like a few grams of vapes, but I mean that's kind of expensive, but
one gram
How much is one of those those disposable ones you always see uh, like mike mike stroke off. He always says the disposable
Vape I guess you get so many hits off it then you just throw it away. How much do yeah, that's what I get boys, right? I
Think those cost
I see one for like 27 years one for 27 bucks
There's one for 30 bucks. So these are the others probably the best deal you'll find a one all-in-one diamonds vape gelato
I wonder if it's from the same store
Sun Valley caregiver. Oh, that's nice. He's far away. Okay cure company Crenshaw
I don't know. I mean hopefully start a new cart. I hopefully can find a good deal
I'm making my walk my French toast in the oven. It's like I gotta get that out. Oh nice French toast beautiful
It's a
Preserve Zion. Hey, Lenore. Oh, here's Lenore. I sit up too fast. Okay
Okay, I'm better. I must fell over. I bet your cat's always trying to get into your food
Well, they you know, they do sometimes but
No, not not you know not too bad like they like my like one look at likes my coffee and like anything like
If you try to talk knock over my coffee and shit, but
I can do that. I had a studio apartment and I had my little tabby and she would always try to get into my food
And I'm like fuck you you're eating better than I am. I'm working at McDonald's for minimum wage
Buy a new freaking Purina cat food because you won't eat the generic stuff
It's like go eat your cat food. Don't you know don't don't be over here trying to get my freaking macaroni
my uh
My generic macaroni go go go eat the shit that I paid for because you won't you won't eat anything else
Yeah, are your cats like that are they picky eaters?
Yeah, they are kind of they don't like really cheap food, you know, they like they have to get them on nicer food
But they're not too picky. They're uh
You know, they like their food. I need to create a username.
It is Psyche, AwakeNs.
I have a can, I walk up to the liquor store.
It's maybe three blocks away from my house.
And it must be an outdoor can that belongs
to this particular house,
because it's always on their stairs.
But,
Every every time I pass it's always on the stairs just me. I want at me like it's saying hi and I say
Hey, buddy, and I give it a good wave and I said, you know what? That's what I like at this point in my life
That's what I like. I love cats, but just to say hi to the cat be friendly to it and then just be on my way
That's my relationship with
I can't afford any other pets at this time.
This guy is back.
Okay, Bobby?
Hey, what's up?
Hi, Bobby.
Hey.
Hey, Bob.
I heard you were talking shit about me.
I was, I was, I was.
Why?
Because that made you look like a loser in front of everybody?
Oh, well, you know, whatever.
Yeah, whatever.
Just admit it.
on your own show. Oh shit.
I'm laughing right now. Oh, you're laughing right now, right? Yeah. You're laughing?
I don't hear you laughing. I'm laughing. Ah ha ha ha! You're a liar. Just like he said
you were a fan of Marilyn Manson. You're a fucking liar. Just admit it.
You're right. I lied about it. I lied about it. I would lie about it.
I don't know about it. Yeah, we all know that you lied about it.
you're funny you're fine well thanks for the entertaining funny looking Bobby Bob
whatever this voice you're trying to put on you sound like a bitch you sound
what are you talking about this game voice what are you talking about fuck
about Marilyn Manson
Fuck him fuck Marilyn. Why are you talking? Why is your fucking boyfriend saying that he was his biggest fan?
Manson is that what you hang your confidence on is knowing about Marilyn Manson?
No, I'm asking you why your boyfriend made such a big deal about it
He did it. He did it. You did. No, he didn't I
Was there I said that he got it. Yeah, I said he got a surgery done so that he could suck his own bing-dong
And then he freaked out like a retard
I didn't hear that's not the way you didn't hear it. You didn't hear it because you're a death retard. I didn't hear it
You can't hear anything. You got potatoes in your ears. You retarded motherfucker. You were putting a piece of fucking shit
You say it made of the maintenance you stupid bitch. Just admit it
I made you look like a fucking retard dude. Like this is my fucking show now
My show motherfucker. Oh you go go fuck yourself
Shut up right now. Oh fuck it was the last time
Why do you sound like a slicker?
I don't know. I don't understand where you're coming from with that
It's so important to you go listen to your Marilyn Manson you stupid fuck about that shit, dude
You were talking about wonder years and Marilyn Manson. I thought I'd show up and school you motherfuckers
That's why I did a great job
I was a little man, son, haha
What about a good?
Hey Bobby, what do you want to know?
Well, you want to know
You live at your parents you and your mom's basement 1,000 percent you are yeah, dude
Totally
Zoomer kind you zoomer kind
Yeah, zoomer corn
That's you you sound like a bitch you sound like you I'm doing an impression of you sound like a zoomer bitch
Go listen. I'm doing an impression of you. You stupid. I'm doing an impression of you though. So you sound like a different bitch
You're my cunt. Oh, yeah at 30. We're gonna hear about it
37 years old. Yep, 37 years. What?
What kind of losers talk about Marilyn Manson to eight people
You do apparently is that not you got a whole show built around it buddy. You can't you can't you can't
Hey, if I walk this my show now if I
Can do about it and wanted it. Hey, if I want to walk up to me
Rope fucking you want to be honest. Is there anything you could do about it? If I was not gonna happen
Didn't you just didn't you just say that you weren't gay though and none of you're talking about this do about it
There's not a stupid little zoomer. You stupid little zoomer. You know how many zoomers are watching your show zero
You're impersonating yourself. I'm impersonating you
If I impersonate myself, that's not an impersonation. That's just me being myself a little bitch
Do you have a high school diploma? You don't you have a high school? Do you have a high school diploma? I do
I have a little kids. Oh really kids an associate and what being gay
Second dick you don't have a high school. Be honest. Do you have a high school diploma? You don't have a college degree
You don't guess for it. I have a degree in business and my business is giving you the business
And guess what motherfucker business is filming parents bitch bitch you live at your parents
Bitch you live with your parents you have a college degree and you live at your parents bitch god damn right
Stupid little we're gonna get about it my stupid. I have a college degree
Well, I already told you if I was there in person. You told me what you wouldn't do that though
It's never gonna happen. It's a fantasy you live in a fantasy world buddy. What would you do?
What would you do? I wouldn't be caught dead hanging around there like you ever
Not gonna happen. You live in a fantasy world man. You live in a world
Well, you have nine fucking people watching your Gash show where you talk about Marilyn Manson and call people Zoomers.
Right, dude!
Right, show dude.
You came on the- I wasn't talking about Marilyn Manson, that was you.
Or you were talking about the Wonder Years and you said something about Marilyn Manson.
Like, fucking everybody watching knows that.
You thought-
Like, you're trying to lie.
Oh, lies.
You just don't like man
I did come back on here. This is my show. What am I gonna do not be on my own show?
Retard
You're a little zoomer who lives at his parents and if I was there in person I
You know that I you know that my fuck you said you lived at your parents. You said that you're yeah, okay
Yeah, what are you gonna do about it though? Are you gonna break it in my house when I'm asleep when I'm all tucked in tender
Hey, three minutes weeks dreaming about how I'm like making fun of you making you look like a reach out in front of everybody
Hey, bitch. You ever saw
Okay
Hey, everyone's leaving everyone's leaving. He's just so annoying everyone thought of leave
So I'm just gonna kick him off because he just be so annoying. So anyway
Um, yeah, that was an interesting person that could not it's anyway. Oh, sorry if I was trying to come here defense
I'm like, what what the fuck is Marilyn Manson? Like is this a Marilyn Manson historian then go listen to your Marilyn Manson like
I don't know what a weirdo
But some people zoomer fucks in their place. Oh, yeah, I have a college degree in business
The fuck he does in he admitted he lives at his parents. I mean, he's a typical zoomer on IP2 and all these other channels
He's just a typical zoomer. I
Probably went overboard there, but it was all in your honor site. Thank you. I appreciate that. I appreciate that
You're a good friend
You're a good friend and I love you
Yes, some might say the friend yes, I would I would just agree at this point like uh, you know, I think uh, you you get me so
I appreciate you being a friend
Bro these little zoomer fucks. There's they talk in circles
They contradict themselves
And uh, it's just an endless cycle. It's just an endless cycle
It's just a damn god damn guy. I mean
What I
Bobby was a bitch is what he was Bobby was a bitch
I know anything then he was like it's my show. I don't know. He's trying to annoy me
I think that by saying that but whatever
Whatever okay
Whatever, whatever dude, whatever dude
I'll I'll regret going off like that in the morning when I sober up
Or maybe I won't remember it. Yeah, I won't even remember no regrets. No regrets. No regrets
See by my website
What else do you
What what else do we got going on? What's on the agenda for tomorrow kind of order for tomorrow?
It's Monday tomorrow. So Monday. I got you know, it's like a nice week ahead of me. Let's see. It's gonna be
Not too much is happening until
You know until next Friday. Well, not I don't even know what's going on then but week is kind of boring
I'm just gonna plan on sleeping in and
Enjoy myself
But you got plan a piece. Oh
God just the usual I got to run some errands tomorrow like I hate having to do anything
like you know what I mean, I truly hate having to do anything but
Yeah, I just gotta take care of a few things tomorrow. I mean, it's nothing major, but
It's like I'm you know, I'm thinking like damn. I actually got a
It is what it is. I I mean goddamn I used to
When I was a younger man a skinnier man like I used to wake up at
Frickin six in the morning and go read utility meters for a
Walk upwards of 10 miles a day and
Frickin driving in rural areas with you know, you can't figure out what address is what and
But that was when I was young and now I'm old and now I'm fat
Well, I hope you have a great week and yeah shit I
Always like talking to you. You're always a great friend of the show
Oh, are you kicking me?
I'm just saying it's awesome talking to you. I love talking to you. I'm cool. I'm just like here
Oh, I'm here filling out this this paperwork trying to get this weed over here, and uh, hopefully I'll do it
If you don't mind me asking what was the what was the last like full-time job you had if you don't mind me asking
Huh go ahead
2008 I was in a 2008 or 2006 to 2008 I worked for an engineering firm that we did outsourcing for like NASA
You know doing the Hubble telescope and different engineering outsourcing and
It was pretty interesting. I was assistant to the CEO and I had a couple some good experiences there, but you know
I just didn't didn't last but
I had a nice two years. I was I was actually the employee of the month a couple times
Last meeting I did was like actually a plaque. No, I got no you get a bonus when you got a employee of the month
But I never a plaque and
Very nice
Yeah, it was even better
Go ahead. I'm sorry. I'm sorry
No, you go ahead. I want to hear you go ahead. No, I was saying I've always had just like
I've always had garbage jobs like throughout my 20s. I mean
The longest thing I ever did was reading utility meters. I did that for like five years just
You know, my little Toyota Corolla sliding all over the place in rural towns in Michigan,
just ice slick roads and whatever not.
And then, I mean, I've worked, my dad, he's ran a few restaurants, I've worked for my
dad part time.
I've been a I've worked for our school as a janitor, but I'll be goddamn. I've never I've never been a consultant for NASA
I can't say I've done that. So we did it. We did it. We did some of the engineering
We did some of like the outsourcing to China. We would send like engineers to China to do the inspection on
stuff like the Hubble telescope and
and so we also client was one of our clients was honey well and
You know, they had some major major clients, but
Yeah, just lasted a couple years and then that was it.
I used to get jobs through, like we have so many staffing agencies here in Grand Rapids
Michigan for manufacturing and I would get a job through a staffing agency.
And they'd be like, okay, show up six in the morning.
I would, so I'd pull into the parking lot
and just look at this building, this factory or warehouse.
And I'd be like, God damn it, I don't want to go in there.
I do not want to go in there and spend the next eight hours.
And I would just leave.
I just put her in drive and leave.
Go back home.
Oh my God.
And then I go.
Later, I would just go to another staffing game and see and get another job
Well, you know, that's how to do it sometimes, you know, it's like
the some of them are not are not like
Jobs that you will regret too much leaving, you know, so
There's not that many great jobs. I
Look at Lomans, too. I know moments. I used to work at Lomans, too. I don't know if you ever heard of Lomans
but uh lomens was uh kind of it's kind of like an off um it's kind of like an off-priced store
it's kind of got a lot of uh really cool like designer brands and stuff but um it's like
overstock stuff and so you can get some good deals and there's a bunch of them in the world um
it was a big chain at the time but now it's not as big anymore I don't think but yeah
lomens was pretty cool I'm not sure if that was ever a thing here in Michigan I don't recognize the uh
I don't recognize the name.
Maybe that was a West Coast thing.
Lowman's, you said, Lowman's?
Yeah, her name was Frida Lowman.
I think her name was Frida Lowman or something like that.
And I'll do the creator of it.
Let me see if I have cash for this one second, 20, 40, 60.
Yep, I do, okay.
All good.
Cash list or cash, okay.
Nice order.
I think I did it.
I ordered it.
Okay, I got a two gram baby coming.
My drunk ass has to walk to the liquor store to get a few more beers before they close
But hey, sorry, okay, I meant well. I meant well. Sorry if I went to you're fine
You're absolutely fine
Hey everybody, okay, let me try for talk to you soon. Okay anytime
Alright, thank you
Hey, I'm sorry if I missed some things so Irby I like to see off on the wonder years when you was hot
Okay, vapor boy Irby ash tap water
Yeah, we're talking about Marilyn Manson. There's a very funny argument. What's up, Dougie? Hey Dougie Doug
Anyone's welcome up on camera
It's 18 people in the chat. Oh rough mountaintop. Good evening Dougie Doug
Yeah
Yeah, and Doug I'll get I'll get Doug back his is his mod hold on
Because I did a mod a bunch of people dug that you're a good mod
So let's see
I'm gonna get back to the one Doug
I want you to promote your to put your channel in the chat if you can so people can subscribe to you. Okay. Oh
Okay
So let me see
You channel
Okay, and then live
Okay. Okay. See y'all. Here we go. Okay, Dougie.
I can get my chat up to come to work. Chat. There we go.
Dougie Doug. There you go. Hopefully everyone's doing good.
I don't know. I've been working on trying to get a screenshot of why my TikTok isn't working.
Let me see if it works yet. They might have fixed it for me.
But it's kind of weird that it doesn't work.
Okay, everyone doing good?
Hopefully summer is back soon and anybody else when I come up on live the
You have the is on
Okay, so it does not work
It doesn't work for some reason
Well, it's gotten pretty quiet in the chat.
If no one talks in the next couple of minutes,
I'll just postpone the rest of summer stream
and come back a little bit later
because it seems like it's kind of quiet right now.
I don't know if you guys got bored with the conversation,
but let's take out my weed and I'll take ahead the weed
and hopefully have a good sleep.
I'll have a little food right now.
58 59 okay one minute
Let summer know if you see her that'll she has another two hours to claim
It seems like it's really quiet right now
Okay, hope everyone had a great day. Thank you guys be in here
I'll come back at 10 o'clock probably and
Maybe nine. It's eight o'clock
Make it nine or ten
Do the other two hours and just take a little breather
See eight o'clock
There oh, there's Lola her name was Lola. Oh
Hi
Good girl. Hi good girl
God's coming
Yo
What's up, it's going on brother. Is this gotty are you been brother? Oh, that's you. It's okay. Hey, gotty. What's up?
I'm good brother. What's up, brother? You're here. Okay. Good. What's going on?
No, I was like if no one came up or talked but you know you came up, so I'm happy to
I wanted to clear up real quick. I want to do it in person. I didn't want to do it from chat
Never said that shit just so you know you heard that you heard that in your mind. Okay, okay?
It was right after him
But after you said that after he said that I said it with the D
So it wouldn't make it sound like he was doing it on your channel
But just like when you say oh in a video game in a video game like a murder like yeah, I got you
You got mad and you fucking flipped out I understand
Like flip out, but yeah, I did kind of flip out. Yeah
If I was like, well, I did that was really that was really for what's his name like, you know, because there was like, you know
Joe I've explained to Joe a million times not to say it, but then I just didn't so I apologize. I apologize for the finger
It's understandable. I don't say that shit. If I'm saying that you'll know it. It's clear as a belt
But when you gave us the finger backstage, then I knew you were kind of mad about the whole thing. I said, oh, poor guy
You got you got offended. He really got a lot
Forgive Joe about it. Like I don't think Joe it really means to meant to do it
But you know, it's like I've explained to him not to do it
And so it kind of pissed me off and then I thought you were piling on it
So I apologize for mishearing sometimes I do and I was a little bit jumped the gun, right?
That's cool. The only thing you should really apologize for because she was hurt was the
spunky thing. That when you talk to her, apologize about that. That's one of the theories.
I will. I will.
That shit is easily fixed. But that stuff with her, you should definitely apologize.
I know as soon as I do I'll fear I mean I did apologize like when she wasn't here
But I do want to give a personal apology when she comes back
It was it was just like you know, I just got I get paranoid sometimes. I probably needed some sleep
I went to bed like right after that and
Slips for like a long time. I feel better and it's like, you know, it's just was a little bit bitchy like
Once you get piled on I know how you get you know, it's a lot to take in
Yeah, I get I get kind of paranoid. Yeah, you're too nice to people man
You cuz you don't want to start fucking hitting the button boom boom boom boom boom and just knocking people out
I know how you are me me. I would fucking knock everybody out of the room. There'd be like two people left in here
Yeah, I'll have nobody on this show, you know, so
Like you said, I can always build another audience. So fuck it
Well, I can but it's like I really would like to maintain my audience. I have and I think that we have great people here right now
And I love everybody. I just
Yeah, it is a good group
You'll be offset. You know what you do work. All right, I'm gonna catch you later. Go get some rest. I'll see you guys
Love you God. Take it easy man. Yeah, you too. Love you. Hey, so yeah, yeah, I will have a good pop, but you know the
It's coming soon. I think I will
Take a little break right now. I'm gonna try to like get my tiktok stuff worked out
I'll be back at probably at nine o'clock or maybe a little maybe nine thirty or maybe ten
I'll come back as soon as possible finish off summer's panel. Hopefully she's um, she's back by that time and
I just love you guys
I'll see you in a little bit. Okay. Thank you. Hope yeah. See you soon